{
    "subject": "Quentin_Tarantino",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "From_Dusk_till_Dawn",
    "human_readable": "Quentin Tarantino acted in From Dusk till Dawn.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9735968708992004,
            "question": "Besides directing, what other role did Quentin Tarantino have in 'From Dusk till Dawn'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6052552461624146,
            "question": "Name a movie where Quentin Tarantino played a role."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5593206882476807,
            "question": "Quentin Tarantino appeared in which film alongside his directing role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4998287558555603,
            "question": "Quentin Tarantino is known for directing, but he also acted in which movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4955905079841614,
            "question": "In what movie did Quentin Tarantino act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4354621171951294,
            "question": "What is the title of the movie where Quentin Tarantino has a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38171955943107605,
            "question": "Can you name a film in which Quentin Tarantino acts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3466969132423401,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that features Quentin Tarantino as an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3465665280818939,
            "question": "Which movie showcases Quentin Tarantino's acting skills?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29611822962760925,
            "question": "What film features both Quentin Tarantino as director and actor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Quentin Tarantino acted in From Dusk till Dawn.",
            "html": "yago_406_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which movie showcases Quentin Tarantino's acting skills?",
            "html": "yago_406_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film that features Quentin Tarantino as an actor?",
            "html": "yago_406_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a film in which Quentin Tarantino acts?",
            "html": "yago_406_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_406_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Quentin Tarantino's appearance in the film \"From Dusk Till Dawn,\" confirming that he did act in this movie."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}